ILR School Reprints of Articles about the School /3061
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Reprints of Articles about the School
1947-1962
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3061
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents), reprints.
Articles published by Cornell University and others regarding the ILR School.
8436142
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 14, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8436142
- Cornell Alumni News - November 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cornell Alumni News - November 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Cornell Alumni News - November 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Cornell Alumni News - November 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 'America" Russian Mag., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 'America" Russian Mag., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 'America" Mag., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Newspapers, Articles, 1947-1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Kiplinger Magazine - The Changing Times, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cornell Alumni News, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Cornell Alumni News, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Cornell Alumni News, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Industrial Bulletin, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Partners - The Magazine of Labor and Management, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Partners - The Magazine of Labor and Management, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Partners - the Magazine of Labor and Management, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Industrial Bulletin, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Historical Materials, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Reprint Alumni News June 15, 1957 Risley (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Reprint -- Business Week, Aug. 4, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Reprint Industrial Bulletin Apr. 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Reprint - 2nd Labor News Conf. Ind. Bull. 1/54, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Reprints from Industrial Bulletin - 1952 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Reprints from Industrial Bulletin, March 1950 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Partners April-May, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Partners April-May, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Partners April-May, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Partners April-May, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Education, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Reprints From Business Week Sept. 1953 (Box 2, Folder 13)